Juan Marcos Cabezas

Colombia



juanmarcoscabezas@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/juanmarcoscabezas

Summary

Software engineer with experience in C, Python, Java, Javascript, and PHP. Who has also been working with Nodejs, React, Vue, Django, and Flask.

His greatest desire is to build a community of software developers in Tumaco, in order to teach people without programming knowledge, and that they can look for job opportunities in tech since unemployment rates in Tumaco are close 74%.

Experience



Software Engineer

Growth Acceleration Partners

Feb 2021 - Present (6 months +)

I Software Engineer

Clean News Media (cleannews.io)

Dec 2019 - Dec 2020 (1 year 1 month)

Responsibilities:

- Development of a Job Board, to recruit Colombian talent in Europe.
- Development of a search engine that centralizes events occurring worldwide from different verified sources.

https://cleannews.io/

Technologies:

- Python, Node, Serverless, React, AWS, DynamoDB, Cognito, PostgreSQL.

Software Engineer

Automotores Comagro s.a

Nov 2020 - Nov 2020 (1 month)

In this project I was working as a software engineer in the development of the Comagro car quotes platform

https://automotorescomagro.com/compraexpress/

Technologies:

- HTML, JavaScript, CSS

Software Engineer

WWF Colombia

Sep 2020 - Nov 2020 (3 months)

In this project I was working as a software engineer in the development of the donations platform of WWF Colombia

https://donacion.wwf.org.co/



Software Engineer

Easy Search

Jul 2020 - Aug 2020 (2 months)

Easy Search is a project in which you can find the price history of products that you want in Falabella, Alkosto and Exito

https://easy-search.herokuapp.com/

Technologies:

- Python, Django, HTML, CSS



🐧 Software Engineer

Torre

May 2020 - Jun 2020 (2 months)

This project was an MVP that allowed validating the possibility of making posts on job offer platforms and have control over their status.

Technologies:

Python, Node, Bash, Mysql, Linux

Software Engineer

Chispa

Apr 2020 - Apr 2020 (1 month)

Responsibilities:

- Build the mobile version for Cali Chispa.

https://cali.chis.pa/

Technologies:

- React, Sass



Software Engineer

Global Circuit Ltda.

Apr 2019 - Sep 2019 (6 months)

Responsibilities:

- Development of a monitoring tool for the status of mobile signal penetration within correctional facilities outside of Colombia.
- Development of a CRM for the management of sales, clients, portfolio, and deliveries.
- Improvements to the architecture, design, front-end, and back-end of web products.

Technologies:

- Node, Express, Angular, Ionic, Vue, Java, MySQL.

Education

Holberton School

Software engineer, Ingeniería de software 2019 - 2021

Universidad de Nariño

Systems engineer, Ingeniería de software 2014 - 2018

Skills

C (Programming Language) • Python • JavaScript • Bash • Java • MySQL • PostgreSQL • Node.js • AngularJS • React.js